Truth can be dangerous...Trust can be deadly.
Antitrust is a action, crime, drama film directed by Peter Howitt.
A computer programmer's dream job at a hot Portland-based firm turns nightmarish when he
discovers his boss has a secret and ruthless means of dispatching anti-trust problems.
Milo Hoffman, played by Ryan Phillippe.
Lisa Calighan, played by Rachael Leigh Cook.
Gary Winston, played by Tim Robbins.
Alice Poulson, played by Claire Forlani.
Lyle Barton, played by Richard Roundtree.
Larry Banks, played by Tygh Runyan.
Antitrust (also titled Conspiracy.com and Startup) is a 2001 American
techno-thriller film directed by Peter Howitt and written by Howard Franklin.
The film stars Ryan Phillippe, Rachael Leigh Cook,
Claire Forlani and Tim Robbins.
It portrays young idealistic programmers and a large corporation (NURV) that offers a significant salary, an informal
working environment, and creative opportunities for those talented individuals willing to work for them.
The charismatic CEO of NURV seems to be good-natured, but new employee Milo Hoffman
begins to unravel the terrible hidden truth of NURV's operation.
Antitrust opened in the United States on January 12, 2001 to generally negative reviews from critics,
and was a box office failure, grossing $18 million against a budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of computer, hacker, technology, minidisc, garage.
The tone is emotional.